daily routines
hi mom i'm enjoying life
in new zealand the countryside
is so beautiful
[Applause]
my routine is different now
i wake at six o'clock every morning
and go for a run
at seven o'clock i have breakfast
the coffee in new zealand is so
good at eight o'clock
i go to work
i usually take the bus
but sometimes i walk
i start work at nine o'clock
i work in my office until lunchtime
at 12 o'clock i have lunch with my
colleagues
in the park it's nice
to enjoy the fresh air and chat together
at five o'clock i leave work
and go to the gym
i exercise until 6 15
and then go home
at 8 o'clock i eat dinner
then relax i normally
go to bed at 11 30.
see you soon stephen
[Music]
foreign
you